Contact

+918889437667 (Mobile) anandabhinav27@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhinavanand-56968380 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Foreign Exchange Management
International Trade
Customer Relationship Management
(CRM)

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Maithili (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Vocational Training, BSNL
Embedded Systems
Vocational Training, All India Radio
National Conference on VLSI,
Communication and Nanoelectronics
TECHKRITI 2014

Abhinav Anand

Relationship Manager, ICICI Bank Gwalior, Madhya Pradesh, India

Summary

I am currently serving as Relationship Manager , Foreign Exchange Services with special

focus on NRI and Wealth Segment Remittances(Sales). I have also worked in Elite Trade

Relationship Group(Sales) with focus on Export-Import and Assets.

Experience

ICICI Bank

5 years 1 month

Relationship Manager, Forex Services November 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months) Gwalior, Madhya Pradesh, India

Relationship Manager, Foreign Exchange Services November 2018 - October 2021 (3 years) Mumbai

RM - FOREX

Relationship Manager, Elite Trade Relationship Group January 2018 - October 2018 (10 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

RM - ETRG

Manipal Academy of Higher Education Probation Officer May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Education

ICICI Manipal Academy, Bangalore Post Graduate Diploma In Banking (2017) Maharana Pratap College Of Technology, Gwalior Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Electronics and Communication Engineering · (2011 - 2015)

Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 5, Gwalior High School, SCIENCE · (1999 - 2011)